Mazyad Aljaramani

PHOTOGRAPHER AND VIDEOGRAPHER

() +971 52 6199709



@ mazyadalj1190@gmail.com



PROFILE -

Professional Photographer and videographer with 4+ years of experience. Seeking to craft memorable images and videos, for personal and professional purposes, and my passion in photography and videography lead me to start a profession as a graphic designer and video editer.

WORK EXPERIENCE IN UAE

Photographer, Videographer

Kapech me - Dubai From 0CT-2020 until now

- ◆ Setting up photographic equipment & taking pictures
- Editing and retouching images & choosing and setting up locations
- Reproducing and framing photographs & promoting their business
- Rsearching and making contacts & general administration.

Graphic designing:

- ◆ Planning concepts by studying relevant information and materials.
- Illustrating concepts by designing examples of art arrangement, size, type size and style and submitting them for approval.
- Preparing finished art by operating necessary equipment and software.
- ◆ Contributing to team efforts by accomplishing tasks as needed.
- Communicating with clients about layout and design.
- Creating a wide range of graphics and layouts for product illustrations with software such as photoshop.

Photographer, Videographer

Freelancer.

From JAN-2020 until now

- capturing memories through video and pictures
- capturing content for advertising campaigns
- capturing all product content including but not limited to food & drink, venue, staff, etc.

Video editer

Freelancer.

Graphic designer

From JAN-2020 until now

- storyboarding
- Using adobe (premiere pro, and after effects) to edit videos.
- Using adobe adobe audition for basic sound editing.

IN SYRIA

Communication Coordinator

At Syria Trust for Development From APR-2018 until DEC-2019

- ◆ Capture, edite and archive videos and pictures for the organization activities in all it's departments.
- manage social media accounts
- design social media posts and printing posters banners etc
- Designing professional presentations using (Powerpoint and Illustrator)
- planning for social activities and events.
- Prepare weekly and monthly inner Reports.

Internal Volunteer At Syria Trust for Development From JAN-2017 until APR-2018 Outreach Volunteer At Syria Trust for Development From JUN-2016 until JAN-2017 Freelancer. Photographer, Videographer From JAN-2016 until DEC 2019

EDUCATION -

DEGREE OF MASS MEDIA COMMUNICATIONS

Syrian Virtual University Student

TECHNICAL SKILLS -

ADOBE SUITE

photoshop	••••	V Good
premiere pro	••••	Good
illustrator	••••	Good
Audition	••••	Good
after effects	••••	Basic

OTHER SOFTWARES

powerpoint	••••	V Good
Excel	••••	V Good

SPECIALIZED SKILLS -

- ◆ Handling cameras Canon, Nikon, Sony & Panasonic.
- ◆ Handling imaging equipment, (Ronin S.... etc).

NON-TECHNICAL SKILLS -

- Creativity
- Customer Care
- Organized & Cooperative
- Problem-solving
- Adaptiveness
- ◆ Team Collaboration
- ◆ Work under pressure

COURSES -

◆ Advanced Excel	IECD	2019
◆ Social marketing	IECD	2018
◆ Social Media	MAHARA PLATFORM	2020
◆ Photography	LINKDIN	2020
◆ Digital marketing	MAHARA PLATFORM	2020
◆ ICDL	IECD	2019

LANGUAGES		
Arabic	••••	V Good
English	••••	Good

PERSONAL INFORMATION -

Nationality	Syrian
Gender	Male
Date of birth	28 - JAN - 1993
Visa status	Resident
Driving License	UAE